$obody_option_refit	Enable ORefit
$obody_option_nipple	Enable nipple randomization
$obody_option_genitals	Enable genitals randomization
$obody_option_preset_key	Presets list key
$obody_option_reset_distribution	Reset all distributed presets
$obody_option_reset_actor	Reset this actor:
$obody_message_box_option_yes	Yes
$obody_message_box_option_no	No
$obody_highlight_refit	(Save and reload to take effect) Makes it so that when an actor is clothed, sliders are changed to simulate the effect clothes have on the different body parts. Works fine with CBBE and UNP based bodies, including CBBE 3BA and BHUNP from my tests. Disable if you get weird results.
$obody_highlight_nipple	(Save and reload to take effect) Randomizes nipples with procedural generation. Supposedly only works in CBBE based bodies.
$obody_highlight_genitals	(Save and reload to take effect) Randomizes genitals with procedural generation. Supposedly only works in CBBE 3BA body.
$obody_highlight_preset_key	Set the key which shows the menu of all installed presets.\nIf an NPC is in your crosshair, it will apply the preset to the NPC. If an NPC is NOT in your crosshair, it will apply the preset to your Player Character.
$obody_highlight_reset_distribution	Reset the presets that have been distributed to NPCs. This will respect the rules you set in the JSON configuration. Please do this on a cell with no other NPCs or with as few NPCs as possible, such as a player home. Also please note this will only take effect after you save and then reload the game.
$obody_highlight_reset_actor	Completely reset the morphs that OBody NG has applied to the actor in the crosshair. To reset the Player character, simply have nothing in your crosshair.
$obody_message_reset_distribution	All presets that have been distributed to NPCs will be reset. Your JSON configuration rules will be respected.\n\nPLEASE do this on a cell with no other NPCs or with as few NPCs as possible, such as a player home or even a dungeon.\n\nYou will need to save and exit the game afterwards. Do you want to proceed?
$obody_message_reset_distribution_success	OBody NG will reset the presets that have been distributed.\n\n PLEASE SAVE THE GAME AND EXIT THE GAME NOW! Then start Skyrim and reload your save again. This is needed for the reset to work!
$obody_message_reset_actor	Morphs applied by OBody NG to the actor in the crosshair have been reset.
