$obody_option_refit	Enable ORefit
$obody_option_nipple_sliders_orefit	Enable ORefit nipple morphing
$obody_option_nipple	Enable nipple randomization
$obody_option_genitals	Enable genitals randomization
$obody_option_performance_mode	Enable Performance Mode
$obody_option_respectful_morph_application	Enable respectful morph application
$obody_option_force_preset_application_immediate	Force immediate preset application
$obody_option_preset_key	Presets list key
$obody_option_reset_distribution	Reset all distributed presets
$obody_option_reset_actor	Reset this actor:
$obody_message_box_option_yes	Yes
$obody_message_box_option_no	No
$obody_message_performance_mode	Performance mode will be disabled. This might result in stutters/FPS dips as you travel across Skyrim.\n\nIt is NOT recommended to turn off Performance Mode in most cases.\n\nIf you want to proceed, click Accept.
$obody_highlight_refit	Makes it so that when an actor is clothed, sliders are changed to simulate the effect clothes have on the different body parts. Works fine with CBBE and UNP based bodies, including CBBE 3BA and BHUNP from my tests. Disable if you get weird results. Character redressing is required for changes to this setting to take effect.
$obody_highlight_nipple_sliders_orefit	If you get sunken or weird nipples/areolas with ORefit, turn off this option to alleviate the problem. Character redressing is required for this to take effect.
$obody_highlight_nipple	Randomizes nipples with procedural generation. Supposedly only works in CBBE based bodies.
$obody_highlight_genitals	Randomizes genitals with procedural generation. Supposedly only works in CBBE 3BA body.
$obody_highlight_performance_mode	With performance mode enabled, you may see body morphs being applied to the NPCs when you meet them for the first time, which can look jarring. However, this happens very rarely, and only when you meet them for the first time! If you turn off Performance Mode, it may result in stutters/FPS dips in large mod lists or older hardware setups. Therefore, it is NOT recommended to turn off Performance Mode in most cases.
$obody_highlight_respectful_morph_application	By default, OBody resets all the morphs of an NPC before applying a preset, including the morphs not originating from OBody. When this setting is enabled, OBody will reset only the morphs originating from OBody, which may improve compatibility with other mods that apply body morphs to NPCs.
$obody_highlight_force_application_immediate	Due to a Racemenu/SSE Engine Fixes bug, sometimes the preset application from the preset list menu is not visually immediate. OBody works around this by redressing the main outfit piece of the character, which forces the new body morphs to apply immediately. If you don't like the visual effect this causes, turn this option off.
$obody_highlight_preset_key	Set the key which shows the menu of all installed presets.\nIf an NPC is in your crosshair, it will apply the preset to the NPC. If an NPC is NOT in your crosshair, it will apply the preset to your Player Character.
$obody_highlight_reset_distribution	Reset the presets that have been distributed to NPCs. This will respect the rules you set in the JSON configuration. Please do this on a cell with no other NPCs or with as few NPCs as possible, such as a player home. Also please note this will only take effect after you save and then reload the game.
$obody_highlight_reset_actor	Completely reset the morphs that OBody NG has applied to the actor in the crosshair. To reset the Player character, simply have nothing in your crosshair.
$obody_message_reset_distribution	All presets that have been distributed to NPCs will be reset. Your JSON configuration rules will be respected.\n\nPLEASE do this on a cell with no other NPCs or with as few NPCs as possible, such as a player home or even a dungeon.\n\nYou will need to save and exit the game afterwards. Do you want to proceed?
$obody_message_reset_distribution_success	OBody NG will reset the presets that have been distributed.\n\n PLEASE SAVE THE GAME AND EXIT THE GAME NOW! Then start Skyrim and reload your save again. This is needed for the reset to work!
$obody_message_reset_actor	Morphs applied by OBody NG to the actor in the crosshair have been reset.
